(Amy:)Ooh, that sounds like fun.
(Penny:)You're kidding, right? We're not just
gonna get drunk and go on rides?
(Amy:)Come on, do it with us.
Ah, all right, whatever. How does it work?
(Bernadette:)Okay, so you pick your princess,
Sleeping Beauty, Snow White, Cinderella.
(Bernadette:)They give you hair, makeup, the works.
I guess it would be fun to be Cinderella.
(Amy:)- I want to be Cinderella too.
- Yeah.
(Bernadette:)We can't all be Cinderella.
(Amy:)Then how do we decide?
(Bernadette:)Well, it's simple. This was my idea,
I'm driving, I'm Cinderella.
(Bernadette:)You bitches got a problem with that,
we can stop the car right now.
(Raj:)Excuse me.
(Raj:)I'm meeting a girl here.
It's kind of a first date.
(Man:)In a library?
(Raj:)She and I are both a little awkward in social
situations so this seemed like a good idea.